hotnewsworld.com 2018-12-26

# Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

**HotNewsWorld.com respects your privacy.**

Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of HotNewsWorld.com.

**Credit card details**

HotNewsWorld.com will never ask for Credit Card details and request that you do not enter it on any of the forms on HotNewsWorld.com.

**External Sites**

HotNewsWorld.com is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.

**Cookies**

A “cookie” is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows HotNewsWorld.com to recognize you each time you visit this site(customisation etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and HotNewsWorld.com does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as newsfeeds.

**Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet**

While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to HotNewsWorld.com and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through HotNewsWorld.com have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.

Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.

At www.hotnewsworld.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.hotnewsworld.com and how it is used.

**Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, www.hotnewsworld.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

www.hotnewsworld.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.hotnewsworld.com.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.hotnewsworld.com and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….  
Google Adsense  
Commission Junction  
Adbrite  
Clickbank

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.hotnewsworld.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.hotnewsworld.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices.  www.hotnewsworld.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

All copyright issues including others will only be dealt in Indian court of Law. All disputes and cases will be solved in New Delhi, India only.

**_If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at hotnewsworld@gmail.com._**
